Diseases like cancer and heart attack
may seem
[Music]
unreal, but we all know
someone who had to spend a lot of money
in the battle for their
life. The high cost of treatment can
deplete most of your savings in one go.
And that's why with ICICA credential
heart and cancer protect you receive
payout right on
diagnosis. The best part is that for the
rest of the policy term premium gets
completely waved
[Music]
off and since you can't schedule a major
disease you get a long-term cover for a
total of 40
years in this affordable plan. A cover
of 10 lak rupees is available at a
premium of just 61 rupees per month. The
benefits don't end here. View this plan
at icicrolife.com.
[Music]